aristotle.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy Policy and Data Restrictions - Aristotle

Aristotle has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Aristotle and its divisions.

## Website

Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products and services. We collect visitor’s contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

This site has security measures in place, including server password and firewalls, to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

* * *

## Copyright Notice

© 1983-2015 Aristotle. All rights reserved.

* * *

## Trademarks

ARISTOTLE, the “Digital Fountain” logo, INTEGRITY, the Integrity “Star Burst” logo, and other trademarks are trademarks of Aristotle Incorporated and may not be used without permission.

* * *

## Political Data Restrictions

Use of and access to voter list data is restricted in some jurisdictions. For information, contact an Aristotle representative. Searching for individual voters is not available, and voter names and addresses are not visible during your searches.

Any information copied, or otherwise obtained, from any FEC report or statement, or any copy, reproduction, or publication thereof, filed under the Act, shall not be sold or used by any person for the purpose of soliciting contributions or for any commercial purpose, except that the name and address of any political committee may be used to solicit contributions from such committees.

* * *

## Use of Data for Verification Purposes

Personally identifiable information provided for purposes of age and identity verification to Aristotle and its Integrity unit is used only for that purpose, and is not transferred or retained, except as required by law.

* * *

## U.S.-EU Safe Harbor and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework Privacy Statement

Aristotle complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Aristotle has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Aristotle’s certification, please visit [here](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

* * *

## Information Obtained from Death Master File (DMF) Subject to Regulation

Certain data provided by Aristotle may include information obtained from the Death Master File (DMF) made available by the US Department of Commerce National Technical Information Service (NTIS) and subject to regulations found at 15 CFR Part 1110. All Aristotle clients are required to comply with all applicable laws and, if Subscriber is granted access to DMF data, Subscriber certifies compliance with 15 CFR Part 1110. Subscriber’s failure to comply with 15 CFR Part 1110 may subject Subscriber to penalties under 15 CFR 1110.200 of $1,000 for each disclosure or use, up to a maximum of $250,000 in penalties per calendar year.

* * *

## Confidentiality of Information/Correction

This site does not provide visitors’ information to third parties. This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:  
Email to [remove@aristotle.com](mailto:remove@aristotle.com)

* * *

## Contacting Aristotle

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact Aristotle at:

**Aristotle**  
205 Pennsylvania Avenue, SE  
Washington, DC 20003  
Phone: (202) 543-8345  
Email: [info@aristotle.com](mailto:info@aristotle.com)
